What's going through your head? What are your feelings? What are your community members feeling
right now? We're all heartbroken. We're nurses. We care about people. He was a caretaker and a
helper. And we're here to speak the truth, the lies that they're spreading. If I were to get
shot today, I'm a school nurse. I work with children. I get up every day and all of us get
every day to take care of people. Don't believe the lies. They're trying to cover up their
brutality and their lack of compassion and their hatred. And we're here to speak the
truth. The same thing they saw. They saw a man step forward to help a woman who had been
shoved to the ground, who was peacefully protesting. They saw that too. And they immediately must
have all gotten together to crush his reputation, this caring individual, to make up lies, to
continue to feed their machine of hatred. I mean, we all saw it. They know they're lying.
We know they're lying. Do they think we're all stupid? I mean, it's just incredible. And
to crush these humans. Renee, she was a poet and a mom. She had a teddy bear in her car.
He was helping someone who was shoved to the ground brutally. I mean, it's lies and we have
to speak the truth and they're not fooling anyone.